Jane Harman Papers, 1960-1998 (ongoing) (bulk 1993-1998)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS 1992-98
  - Videotapes
    - 1996
      - Remarks by Congresswoman Jane Harman for "No to Violence" Campaign, Harriman Communications Center, 12 Jul (Box 253)
      - "Defense Spending," CNN Early Prime, 15 Jul (Box 253)
      - "On a Wing and a Prayer," Dateline, 6 Aug (Box 253)
      - "FAA Meeting," LA CityView, 13 Aug (Box 253)
      - "FAA Meeting," Harriman Communications Center, 13 Aug 1996 (Box 254)
      - * Week in Review, 23 Aug (Box 254)
      - * "Beijing, One Year later," taped message by Harman, 24 Sep (Box 254)
      - Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 4 Oct, [U-Matic tape, see Box 265] (Box 254)
      - Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 4 Oct (Box 254)
      - "24th Congressional District," 5 Oct (Box 254)
      - "Advanced Technology Transit Bus (ATTB) Rollout," 8 Oct (Box 254)
      - "Public Hearing on Aerospace/SAIC Merger, Chaired by Representative Jane Harman," The Aerospace Corporation, 18 Oct (Box 254)
      - "36th U.S. Congressional Debate, Harman vs. Brooks," Jean Carpenter (producer), Continental Harbor Cable, 19 Oct (Box 254)
      - * "One on One, a Conversation with Gary Cox," 15 Nov, [associated written material, see also Box 239] (Box 254)
      - "Friends of Jane Harman," 5 Dec [Betamax] (Box 254)
      - "Morning News, Harman and Steve Buyer, Aberdeen Congressional Visit," 12 Dec, [associated written material, see also Box 239] (Box 254)
      - "A Few Good Women, the Crucible," Nightly News, NBC, 16 Dec 1996 (Box 255)
      - "Perspectives: With Congressman Xavier Becerra and Congresswoman Jane Harman," Continental Cablevision, 17 Dec (Box 255)
      - "36th Congressional Forum" (Box 255)
      - "Brooks/Harman Debates" (Box 255)
      - * "Harman/Brooks Debate," Continental Cablevision/AARP (Box 255)
      - * "Republicans for Harman rally, gun control and Brady Law issues" (Box 255)
    - 1997
      - "Community Focus: Featuring Congresswoman Jane Harman," Jan (Box 255)
      - "DDT Del Amo," David Garcia, 3 Mar (Box 255)
      - "Del Amo DDT, 3:30," KCOP voice-over, 3 Mar (Box 255)
      - "Del Amo DDT, 5 and 6 PM," KNBC voice-over, 3 Mar (Box 255)
      - "Beethoven School, Netday Follow Up," Midday, NBC, 31 Mar (Box 255)
      - * "National Security Committee Hearing on Counterterrorism," Mar 1997 (Box 256)
      - "First Business, Dan Kush Report with Rep. Jane Harman (D-CA)," 2 Apr (Box 256)
      - "Jane Harman," Early Edition, CNN, 30 Apr (Box 256)
      - * "Aberdeen Sex Scandal," "Clinton Budget Deal," CNN and Fox interview, 8 May (Box 256)
      - "Congressional Arts Competition," 19 May (Box 256)
      - "Congressional Arts Competition," 19 May, [U-Matic videotape, see Box 264] (Box 256)
      - "Lewis M. Herman Public Affairs Award," 19 May, [U-Matic videotape, see Box 264] (Box 256)
      - * "Defense Industry in California," Loyola Marymount University, C-SPAN, 30 May (Box 256)
      - Meet the Press, 8 Jun (Box 256)
      - "Rep. Harman and Defense Secretary William Cohen," C-SPAN, 18 Jun (Box 256)
      - "Budget Deal," Jane Harman with Barney Frank, FOX on Politics, 1 Jul (Box 256)
      - "National Security Subcommittee Hearing: Army Plan to Prevent Sexual Misconduct," Jul (Box 256)
      - "North Korea Press Conference," 13 Aug (Box 256)
      - "Korean Independence Day," Korean news stations, Los Angeles, 15 Aug 1997, [associated written material, see also Box 239] (Box 257)
      - "Army Sex Report with Comments by JH," CNN, 11 Sep (Box 257)
      - "DeLeon Project," 16 Sep (Box 257)
      - "DLC Convention: Subject Fast Track," 27 Oct (Box 257)
      - "International Trade and the Economy," Democratic Leadership Council, C-SPAN, 27 Oct (Box 257)
      - "Sen. Kyl's Report to 'Arizonia [sic]: Bolistic [sic] Missile Threat," Oct [Betamax] (Box 257)
      - "Sen. Kyl's Report to 'Arizonia [sic]: Bolistic [sic] Missile Threat," Oct [VHS] (Box 257)
      - "Chinese President's Visit," Hughes and China, Headline News, CNN, 1 Nov (Box 257)
      - "Iran/Russia," Ralph Begleiter, CNN, 5 Nov (Box 257)
      - Floor Statements and Debate on HConRes 121 (Russian Resolution), 5-6 Nov (Box 257)
      - "Lawmakers, Congresswoman Harman," MediaOne, 11 Nov (Box 257)
      - * "Lomita Veteran's Day," Headline News, CNN, 11 Nov 1997 (Box 258)
      - Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 14 Nov (Box 258)
      - * "LAX Town Hall Meeting," LA CityView, 12 Dec (Box 258)
      - "LAX Town Hall Meeting," LA CityView, 12 Dec, [U-Matic videotape, see Box 264] (Box 258)
      - "Iran Arms," CNN, 31 Dec (Box 258)
      - "Kassebaum Report," ABC, Dec (Box 258)
      - "36th Annual Arts Competition, Joslyn Gallery, Torrance, CA," June Armstrong (producer) (Box 258)
      - "Kelly Flinn," NBC News (Box 258)
      - "PTOA/APTS Promo '97" (Box 258)
    - 1998
      - "Sonny, We'll Miss You, Babe," KTLA, 5 Jan (Box 258)
      - Crossfire, CNN, 7 Jan; Primetime News, CNN, 8 Jan (Box 258)
      - "Rep. Jane Harman," Mornings on 2, KTVU/Fox, 25 Mar (Box 258)
      - * "Harman for Governor," Morris and Carrick, 26 Mar 1998 (Box 259)
      - "Harman for Governor: Neighborhood; Fifteen; Jaws; Follow Up; Real," Morris and Carrick, 21 Apr (Box 259)
      - * "Harman for Governor: Neighborhood; Fifteen; Jaws; Follow Up," Morris and Carrick (Box 259)
      - "Los Angeles Times Forum," KCBS, 13 May (Box 259)
      - Life and Times, KCET, 15 May (Box 259)
      - "Harman for Governor: Speak Out," Morris and Carrick, 20 May (Box 259)
      - "Memorial Day Personal Care Day for the Homeless," KTLA, 25 May (Box 259)
      - "Concession Speech," Prime 9 News, KCAL, 2 Jun (Box 259)
      - "Lowey-Harman Amendment, HR 2709-Final Debate, FY 99, DoD Auth.," 9 Jun; "Iran Bill," 9 Jun (Box 259)
      - Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 14 Aug (Box 259)
      - Hannity and Colmes, 18 Aug 1998 (Box 260)
      - "Investigating the President," Larry King Live, CNN, 26 Aug (Box 260)
      - Larry King Live, 26 Aug (Box 260)
      - Jane Harman on Eyewitness News, 10 Sep (Box 260)
      - MSNBC with Brian Williams, 11 Sep (Box 260)
      - "San Francisco Gubernatorial Debate," Stan Statham, Executive Director California Broadcasters Association, 15 Oct (Box 260)
      - "Sonny Bono's death," KTLA News; "Harman/Riggs," Hannity and Colmes, 23 Oct (Box 260)
      - "Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors," Network Television Time, 3 Nov (Box 260)
    - Undated
      - "At Home on Catalina Island," local news features with Linda Garvey, Elanjae Productions Video/Linda Garvey Enterprises (Box 260)
      - "B-2 Bomber," NBC News, 4 Aug (Box 260)
      - * "Candidate Forum," Steve Fowler interview (Box 260)
      - "Community Focus #12 (SBACC)" (Box 261)
      - "Congressional Art Competition;" "Harman Fundraiser at Torrance Park;" "Rep. Primary Debate;" "Bob Dole/Brooks Fundraiser" (Box 261)
      - "Defense Authorization FY 95;" "U.S. House of Representatives, Recognition of members," CNN; "Army Sex Scandal," C-SPAN (Box 261)
      - Dub of Harman, quick cuts, no audio, [tape case damaged] (Box 261)
      - "Fighting for Medicare," informational (Box 261)
      - "From Around LA" (Box 261)
      - "Governor Candidate Statement" (Box 261)
      - * "Gun Control Forum," Paragon Cable (Box 261)
      - "Harman for Governor," Morris and Carrick (Box 261)
      - "Harman for Governor: Cause; Courage," Morris and Carrick (Box 261)
      - "Harman for Governor: Hilda; Loretta; Gloria," Morris and Carrick (Box 261)
      - "Harman for Governor: Truth," Morris and Carrick (Box 262)
      - Interview regarding President Clinton's economic package and energy tax, Day Watch, CNN (Box 262)
      - "JH in District; JH Doing Stuff" (Box 262)
      - "JH - Speech/Debate Prep" (Box 262)
      - "LAX," Congressional Update, Steve Mayer (Box 262)
      - "Medicare Debate," Henninger Capitol (Box 262)
      - "Meet the Press plus Rep. Buyer--Kelly Flynn [sic]" (Box 262)
      - "P.I.C. Award Luncheon: Congresswoman Harmon's [sic] Address," City of Torrance Office of Cable Communications (Box 262)
      - "Rep. Harman," Nightline, ABC (Box 262)
      - "Roy's Tape" (Box 262)
      - Jane Harman, Show and Segment (Box 262)
      - "Spotlight: Clips," sample tape of TV show (Box 263)
      - "Susan Brooks Campaign Kickoff" (Box 263)
      - "Susan Brooks," C-SPAN (Box 263)
      - * "Technology Forum," Paragon Cable (Box 263)
      - "Up Close: Jane Harman" (Box 263)
      - "Women in Combat, House Armed Services Committee," The World Today, CNN (Box 263)
      - "Women in Congress: Making a Difference" (Box 263)
      - "Women in the U.S. Military: After the Tailhook Scandal," Newsmaker Saturday, CNN (Box 263)
    - U-Matic
      - "Congressional Arts Competition," 19 May 1997 (Box 264)
      - "LAX Town Hall Meeting," LA CityView, 12 Dec 1997 (Box 264)
      - "Lewis M. Herman Public Affairs Award," 19 May 1997 (Box 265)
      - Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 4 Oct 1996 (Box 265)
    - Use copies of videotapes
      - Nightline, 3 Mar 1993 (Box 266)
      - Interview regarding Clinton economic package: Deficit reduction, CNN and Company, 21 May 1993 (Box 266)
      - Speech for High Technology Council Awards, 15 Jun 1993 (Box 266)
      - "Vice President Al Gore Visits TRW: Los Angeles Television Coverage," TRW Media Center, 22 Jun 1993 (Box 266)
      - "No on NAFTA, San Pedro rally," 18 Aug 1993 (Box 266)
      - "Budget House Vote," Inside Politics with Eric Altsheel, 9 Sep 1993 (Box 266)
      - Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 3 Dec 1993 (Box 266)
      - Interview regarding the resignation of Les Aspen [sic], CNN and Company; and C-SPAN hearing, 20 Dec 1993 (Box 266)
      - "Keynote Address: Jane Harmon [sic]," Law Enforcement for the 21st Century Conference, 20-22 Jun 1994 (Box 266)
      - "Harman: Border; Daily," Doak, Shrum, Harris, Carrier, and Devine, 1 Nov 1994 (Box 266)
      - "Direct Access: Congresswoman Jane Harman," 19 Apr 1995 (Box 266)
      - "The U.S. Congress and You: Representative Jane Harman," sponsored by Northrop Corporation, Andrew E. Manatos, Committee for Citizens Awareness, 22 Jun 1995 (Box 267)
      - Week in Review, 27 Oct 1995 (Box 267)
      - "Roundtable," Cox Communications, Inc., 23 May 1996 (Box 267)
      - "An Interview with Jane Harman," Paragon Cable Community FOC, Jun 1996 (Box 267)
      - "Crime Roundtable," The Aerospace Corporation, 3 Jul 1996 (Box 267)
      - Week in Review, 23 Aug 1996 (Box 267)
      - "Beijing, One Year Later," taped message by Harman, 24 Sep 1996 (Box 267)
      - "One on One, a Conversation with Gary Cox," 15 Nov 1996 (Box 267)
      - "Harman/Brooks Debate," Continental Cablevision/AARP, 1996 (Box 267)
      - "Republicans for Harman rally, gun control and Brady Law issues," 1996 (Box 267)
      - "Republicans for Harman rally, gun control and Brady Law issues," 1996 Mar 1997 (Box 267)
      - "Aberdeen Sex Scandal," "Clinton Budget Deal," CNN and Fox interview, 8 May 1997 (Box 268)
      - "Defense Industry in California," Loyola Marymount University, C-SPAN, 30 May 1997 (Box 268)
      - "Lomita Veteran's Day," Headline News, CNN, 11 Nov 1997 (Box 268)
      - "LAX Town Hall Meeting," LA CityView, 12 Dec 1997 (Box 268)
      - "Harman for Governor," Morris and Carrick, 26 Mar 1998 (Box 268)
      - "Harman for Governor: Neighborhood; Fifteen; Jaws; Follow Up," Morris and Carrick, 1998 (Box 268)
      - "Candidate Forum," Steve Fowler interview, undated (Box 268)
      - "Gun Control Forum," Paragon Cable, undated (Box 268)
      - "Technology Forum," Paragon Cable, undated (Box 268)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Biographical materials, [see also Box 270] (Box 268)
    - Awards/certificates, 1995-96, undated (Box 269)
  - Political activities
    - "Will this Queens Housewife Be the Next Vice President?," East Side Express, v.7, no. 377, 27 Oct-3 Nov 1983 (Box 269)
    - 36th district (CA) map (Box 269)
    - House race, 1992: newspaper clippings (Box 269)
    - Governor's race, 1998: newspaper clippings (Box 269)
  - Legislative files
    - Photograph, President Clinton speaking at podium in front of White House, undated (Box 269)
    - House National Security Committee photograph, 104th Congress (Box 269)
    - "Crying Uncle," The Floridian, 14 Feb 1982 (title pages only) (Box 269)
    - American Maritime Officer, v.25, no.1, Jan 1995 (Box 269)
    - American Maritime Officer, v.26, no.2, Feb 1996 (Box 269)
    - Religious Leaders in Support of Immigration Reform poster (Box 269)
    - "Boeing 27" State Summary poster (Box 269)
    - "Boeing 27" State Summary poster The Fort Jackson Leader, v.37, no.32, 15 Jan 1998 (Box 269)
  - Constituent services
    - Your Rights under the Fair Labor Standards Act poster (Box 269)
    - Around the Region, v.8, no.1-2, Spring/Summer 1995 (Box 269)
    - 30th Anniversary publication, Southern California Association of Governments, 1995 (Box 269)
    - Sierra Club 1996 Voter Guide doorknob hanger (Box 269)
    - Groundwater contaminant plume areas map, Del Amo study area, 22 Oct 1993 (Box 269)
    - Conceptual site plan, Del Amo site, Shell Chemical Company, Del Amo Park, 28 Sep 1998 (Box 269)
    - 36th Congressional District Briefing for the White House Conference on Aging poster (Box 269)
  - Biographical materials: "A Day in the Life of Jane Harman" (Box 270)
  - Political activities
    - Campaign posters and fliers, 1992 (Map-case Flat File)
    - Congressional Women's Caucus poster (Map-case Flat File)
    - Ballona Wetlands blue print (Map-case Flat File)